<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools" tools:ignore="MissingTranslation">

    <string name="google_app_name">WomanCyc</string>
    <string name="yandex_app_name">WomanCyc</string>
    <string name="google_marketing_message">"WomanCyc: calendar of woman's cycle"</string>
    <string name="description">
<![CDATA[
WomanCyc is a simple period tracker application, you can mark in calendar:
 * menstruation days and blood flow intensity;
 * intercourses (protected and unprotected);
 * days when you took pill (if you take oral contraceptives once a day);
 * small notes. there is user interface for autocomplete if you repeat the same notes.

Features of the application:

 * The application may be used by women with regular and irregular menstruation.

 * The application does not impose any restrictions on expected length of cycle, actual length of cycle, or bleeding length. You can edit any days of calendar (also days in future), the application will work correctly.

 * Every day of cycle is numbered beginning with the first day of menstruation. You can estimate how many days are left until the next menstrual period or number of days delay lasts. If your period does not come on time, the numbering of the days continue.

 * The application can use specified or average length of cycle.

 * Calculation of fertile-infertile periods are not made.
 Reasons:
 1) if you want to get pregnant, you should have sex in the middle of your cycle plus or minus one week - in these days an ovulation occurs;
 2) if you don't want to get pregnant, you should not use the calendar-method of identifying fertile-infertile days - it's unsafe.

Features of user interface:

 * to edit cell of calendar make long click (in one-panel mode);
 * to navigate in calendar use buttons «Next/Previous month/day», also you can navigate to specified date;

 * user interface is strict, minimalistic, there are two themes available (dark and light);
 * one-panel or two-panel mode is used depending on size and orientation of the device screen.

Additional features:

 * Statistics.
 * Export and import of user data.
 * Ability to setup password.
 * Widget.

Additional information is available in the help part of the application.

The application is useful for women and men watching the cycle of their girlfriends.

Please send your comments and suggestions at anna.sent@gmail.com.

Key words: calendar, menstrual cycle, menstruation, period, woman calendar, period tracker, menstrual calendar.
]]>
    </string>
    <string name="what_is_new">
<![CDATA[
v1.0.7:
* English translation.
Please send your comments and suggestions about translation at anna.sent@gmail.com.
* Minor improvements.
]]>
    </string>

</resources>