<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools" tools:ignore="MissingTranslation">

    <string-array name="helpTitles">
        <item>Export and import</item>
        <item>Password</item>
        <item>Widget</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="helpParts">
        <item>
<![CDATA[
"Menu items <B>&laquo;Menu-Save data&raquo;</B> (export) and <B>&laquo;Menu-Restore data&raquo;</B> (import).<BR/><BR/>

Files for export and import are stored in root of SD-card, in directory "WomanCyc". If you clear data of the application or uninstall the application then these files will not be deleted.<BR/><BR/>

You can enter file name or select existing file from the list.<BR/><BR/>

Settings of the application (all that is in <B>&laquo;Menu-Settings&raquo;</B>) are NOT saved in this file.<BR/><BR/>

You can clear all entered data by selecting menu item <B>&laquo;Menu-Clear data&raquo;</B> (settings of the application will NOT be cleared).<BR/><BR/>

With export and import you can:<BR/><BR/>

<I> * transfer data from one device to another.</I><BR/><BR/>

<I> * keep data of few users on device.</I>
Save data into files with different names and restore the data for editing.
(Don't forget save data after editing again.)<BR/><BR/>

<I> * backup data.</I>
Make backups of data to SD-card and move the data to another devices, send it by email, save to Dropbox, etc.<BR/><BR/>

<I> * edit pieces of data.</I>
Data is saved in readable format to xml-file,
and you can edit this file by text editor or other program.<BR/><BR/>

Format of the file:<BR/><BR/>

&lt;calendar&gt;<BR/><BR/>

&lt;row _id=&quot;27-03-2013&quot; menstruation=&quot;no&quot; sex=&quot;no&quot; took_pill=&quot;no&quot; note=&quot;note1&quot; /&gt;<BR/><BR/>

&lt;row _id=&quot;28-03-2013&quot; menstruation=&quot;yes&quot; sex=&quot;no&quot; took_pill=&quot;no&quot; note=&quot;note2&quot; /&gt;<BR/><BR/>

&lt;row _id=&quot;13-06-2013&quot; menstruation=&quot;three_drops&quot; sex=&quot;yes&quot; took_pill=&quot;yes&quot; note=&quot;note1&quot; /&gt;<BR/><BR/>

&lt;row _id=&quot;18-06-2013&quot; menstruation=&quot;two_drops&quot; sex=&quot;unprotected&quot; took_pill=&quot;no&quot; note=&quot;&quot; /&gt;<BR/><BR/>

&lt;row _id=&quot;19-06-2013&quot; menstruation=&quot;one_drop&quot; sex=&quot;protected&quot; took_pill=&quot;no&quot; note=&quot;&quot; /&gt;<BR/><BR/>

&hellip;<BR/><BR/>

&lt;/calendar&gt;<BR/><BR/>

Order of records by date does not matter, order of record attributes does not matter.
Spaces and tabs do not matter. Attributes of record may be missing.<BR/><BR/>"
]]>
        </item>
        <item>
<![CDATA[
"If you don't want somebody who have access to your device see your personal data,
then setup password in <B>&laquo;Menu-Settings-Password&raquo;</B>.<BR/><BR/>

<I> * You can send password by email to yourself in order to restore it if you will forget it.</I>
If you select menu item <B>&laquo;Menu-Settings-Send password by email&raquo;</B> the mail application will be opened.
Email address of the device owner will be in the field "To"
(this field will be empty on some devices, in this case you should enter email address by yourself).<BR/><BR/>

<I> * If you forgot password, and:</I><BR/><BR/>
1) you have exported your data to the file or you have not entered important data:<BR/><BR/>
To clear forgotten password you should uninstall and install again the application or clear data of the application
(settings of your device-Applications-WomanCyc-Clear data).
All entered data except the saved (exported) data will be lost.<BR/><BR/>
2) you have NOT exported your data and this data is important for you:<BR/><BR/>
Send me an email at
<A HREF="mailto:anna.sent@gmail.com">anna.sent@gmail.com</A>, you will receive instructions in response.<BR/><BR/>

If you set password then menu item <B>&laquo;Menu-Lock and exit&raquo;</B> will appear.
If you exit from the application using this item, the next time you start the application it will prompt you for a password.<BR/><BR/>

You can check menu item <B>&laquo;Menu-Settings-Automatic locking&raquo;</B>.
In this case the application will prompt you for a password every time you start the application.<BR/><BR/>

If you check menu item <B>&laquo;Menu-Settings-Hide widget&raquo;</B> then content of widget will be hidden if the application is locked with password.<BR/><BR/>"
]]>
        </item>
        <item>
<![CDATA[
There are two configurations of widget:<BR/><BR/>

 * &lt;day of cycle&gt;<BR/><BR/>
 
 * &lt;day of cycle&gt; (&lt;cycle length&gt;)<BR/><BR/>

Specified or calculated (average) value is used as a cycle length
(see menu items <B>&laquo;Menu-Settings-Menstrual cycle&raquo;</B> and <B>&laquo;Menu-Settings-Use average menstrual cycle length&raquo;</B>).<BR/><BR/>

By clicking on the widget the application is started.<BR/><BR/>

By the widget you can determine a delay in your period: for example, &laquo;30 (28)&raquo; &mdash;
today is 30th day of cycle while specified or average length of cycle is 28 days (so, you have 2 days delay of period).<BR/><BR/>
]]>
        </item>
    </string-array>

</resources>